原創翻譯  雙語字幕
最新連載海外影視劇下載
請登陸 www.YYeTs.com
僅供學習  禁止用于任何商業盈利行為
翻譯     Reginamoon x6324 萊吉 吃不胖的毓杰
校對     木淺薰
時間軸     林卡 貝殼 麥克的希德 孫了個大圣 大蔥
后期     吉吉
總監     somehacker
神奇動物在哪里
紐約幽靈報
蓋勒特·格林德沃
黑巫師再次襲擊歐洲
歐洲傲羅做好了戰斗的準備
霍格沃茨魔法學校加強安保措施
黑巫師
恐怖威脅
巫師的困惑
足球是麻雞版魁地奇嗎
格林德沃襲擊
可能引發與麻雞的戰爭
美國持續禁止
私人飼養神奇動物
魔法界暴露危險系數
1926年升至新高
反巫師情緒上漲
皮奎里呼吁大家
保持冷靜
格林德沃身在何處
格林德沃身在何處[德語]
搜捕格林德沃[法語]
還有人能安然度日嗎
格林德沃在全球散布恐懼
杜戈爾  安分點  拜托了
Dougal... you settle down now, please.
用不了很久的
It won't be long.
下一位
Next.
-英國人是吧  -是的
- British, huh? - Yes.
-第一次來紐約嗎  -是的
- First trip to New York? - Yes.
-箱子里有食品嗎  -沒有
- Anything edible in there? - No.
牲畜呢
Livestock?
得拿去修修了  沒有
Must get that fixed... ahh, no.
打開給我看一眼
Let me take a look.
麻瓜模式
-歡迎來到紐約  -謝謝
- Welcome to New York. - Thank you.
下一位
Next!
就像是  像是一陣風
And it was like a... like a wind
或者  像個鬼魂
or like a... like a ghost...
但很黑  我看見了它的眼睛
but dark... and I saw its eyes.
閃閃發光的白眼睛
Shining white eyes...
一股有眼睛的  黑風
A dark wind... with eyes.
一大團黑色物質
Like a dark mass,
然后它朝這里俯沖下來  鉆入了地下
and it dove down there, down underground.
得有人來管管這事兒
Someone ought do something about it.
這玩意無處不在  已經失控了
It's everywhere this thing. It's out of control.
-問出什么嗎  -黑風之類的
- Get anything? - Dark wind, blah blah.
肯定是氣流  或者電流搞的鬼
It's some atmospheric hooey. Or electrical.
-想去喝一杯嗎  -不了  我在戒酒
- Hey, you thirsty? - Nah, I'm on the wagon.
向瑪莎保證了
Promised Martha I'd lay off.
是大氣現象
It's atmospheric.
這座偉大的城市閃耀著人類發明的光輝
This great city sparkles with the jewels of man's invention!
電影院  汽車
Movie theaters, automobiles,
無線電  電燈
the wireless, electric lights.
-無不讓我們眼花繚亂沉迷其中  -抱歉
- All dazzle and bewitch us! - So sorry.
但有光明的地方必有陰影相隨  朋友
But where there is light there is shadow, friend.
有東西正在我們的城市里伺機而動
Something is stalking our city,
造成巨大的傷害
wreaking destruction
然后又消失得無影無蹤
and then disappearing without a trace.
聽好了  我們必須戰斗  加入我們
Listen to me. We have to fight, join us,
加入第二塞勒姆  一起戰斗
the Second Salemers, in our fight!
-借過  小姐  -聽見了嗎
- Excuse me, doll. - You hear me?
-我得去銀行  -我們必須攜手奮戰
- Just trying to get to the bank. - We have to fight together...
-借過  我只是  -看著點路
- Excuse me, trying... - Watch it!
抱歉  是我的箱子
So sorry, my case.
沒事
No harm done.
-借過  -這位朋友
- Excuse me! - You, friend!
是什么驅使你來參加我們今天的集會
What drew you to our meeting today?
我只是路過
Oh... I was just passing.
你是一個找尋者[找球手]嗎
Are you a seeker?
找尋真理之人
A seeker after truth?
其實我更像追尋者[追球手]
I'm more of a chaser, really.
聽我一言  留心我的警告
Hear my words and heed my warning.
敢笑就笑吧
And laugh if you dare.
巫師就在我們之中
Witches live among us!
為了孩子
We have to fight together
為了明天  我們必須并肩作戰
for the sake of our children, for the sake of tomorrow!
你對此有什么看法  朋友
What do you say to that, friend?
失陪
Excuse me.
需要幫忙嗎  先生
Can I help you, sir?
沒有  我只是  在這兒等會兒
No, I was just... just... waiting.
你好
Hi.
你是來辦什么事的
What brings you here?
和你一樣
Same as you...
-你也是來貸款開面包店的嗎  -是的
- You're here to get a loan to open up a bakery? - Yes.
真是好巧啊
What are the odds of that?
-那就讓我們用實力說話吧  -失陪
- Well, may the best man win, I guess. - Excuse me.
先生  先生
Hey, mister... Hey, mister!
伙計
Hey, fella!
科瓦斯基先生  賓利先生現在可以見您了
Mr. Kowalski, Mr. Bingley will see you now.
好吧
Okay...
好的
Okay.
你目前在一個罐頭廠工作是嗎
You are currently working in a canning factory?
這是我能找到的最好的工作了
That's the best I can do...
我24年才回來的
I only got back in 24'.
-從哪回來  -歐洲  先生
- Got back? - From Europe, sir.
是的  我在同盟國遠征軍服役過
Yeah... I was part of the Expeditionary Forces there.
-好的  -科瓦斯基先生
- All right. - Mr. Kowalski.
你一定得嘗嘗甜圈餅
You gotta try the paczki. Okay?
用得是我奶奶的食譜
It's my grandmother's recipe,
橙子味  真是
the orange zest... just...
科瓦斯基先生
Mr. Kowalski,
你能把什么東西抵押給銀行
what do you propose to offer the bank as collateral?
-抵押  -抵押
- Collateral? - Collateral.
如今的機器
There are machines now
一小時能生產上百個甜甜圈
that can produce hundreds of doughnuts an hour...
我知道  我知道
I know, I know,
但它們絕對比不上我做的
but they're nothing like what I can do.
銀行必須保障利益  科瓦斯基先生
The bank must be protected, Mr. Kowalski.
日安
Good day to you.
那位英國先生
Hey, Mr. English guy!
我覺得你的蛋要孵出來了
I think your egg is hatching.
什么  剛剛發生了什么
What? What just happened?
但是
But...
抱歉
Excuse me...
我剛剛  在那里
I was... over there.
我剛剛  是在那里嗎
I was... over there?
-進來吧你  -你好
- In you hop... - Hello?
不行  大家都安分點  待著
No. Everyone settle down. Stay.
杜戈爾  別逼我進去
Dougal, don't make me come in there.
別逼我下去
Don't make me come down there.
絕對不行  阿霍拉洞開
Absolutely not! Alohomora!
貸款不行你就打算偷了是吧
Oh, so you're gonna steal the money, huh?
統統石化
Petrificus Totalus!
賓利先生
Mr. Bingley!
科瓦斯基
Kowalski!
你不是吧
Really?
不  別這樣  瞧
No... Don't do that. Look.
不  不不不  別開槍  別開槍
Oh no... No, no, no. Don't shoot. Don't shoot!
怎么
What?
最后警告你一次  你這個小賊
For the last time, you pilfering pest...
不許碰那些不屬于你的東西
paws off what doesn't belong to you.
我對這一切深表歉意
I'm awfully sorry about all that.
那到底是什么玩意
What the hell was that?
與你無關
Nothing that need concern you.
不幸的是  你看到得太多了
Now unfortunately you have seen far too much,
所以如果你不介意
so if you wouldn't mind...
請在那站好
if you just stand there,
-一下子就好  -好的  沒問題
- this will be over in a jiffy. - Sure, yeah.
抱歉
Sorry...
糟糕
Bugger.
-你是誰  -什么
- Who are you? - I'm sorry?
你是誰
Who are you?
紐特·斯卡曼德  你是哪位
Newt Scamander. And you are?
你箱子里的是什么
What's that thing in your case?
是我的嗅嗅
That's my Niffler.
你這里有
You've got something on your...
迪利維蘭斯·戴恩曾在塞勒姆時期被指控會巫術
看在迪利維蘭斯·戴恩的份上
Why in the name of Deliverance Dane
你為什么放跑那玩意兒
did you let that thing loose?
我不是故意的  是他屢教不改
I didn't mean to, he's incorrigible,
你瞧  一看見閃閃發光的東西
you see, anything shiny,
-他就撲上去了  -你不是故意的
- he's all over the place. - You didn't mean to?
不是
No.
你就找不到更糟糕的時機放跑那玩意兒嗎
You could not have chosen a worse time to let that creature loose!
如今的時局非常嚴峻
We're in the middle of a situation here!
我得把你帶回去
I'm taking you in.
你要把我帶去哪里
You're taking me where?
美國魔法國會
Magical Congress of the United States of America.
身份證明
你在美國魔法國會工作嗎
So, you work for MACUSA?
什么職位  調查員之類的嗎
What are you, some kind of investigator?
拜托你告訴我你處理好了那個麻雞
Can you please tell me you took care of the No-Maj?
處理什么
The what?
麻雞  沒有魔法的人  非巫師
The No-Maj! No-magic... the non-wizard!
抱歉  我們叫他們麻瓜
Oh, sorry, we call them Muggles.
你清除他的記憶了吧
You wiped his memory, right?
拎箱子的那個麻雞
The No-Maj with the case?
這違反了3A條例  斯卡曼德先生
That's a Section 3A, Mr. Scamander.
我得帶你回部里
I'm taking you in.
來吧
Come on.
抱歉  但說真的我還有事要做呢
Er... sorry, but I do have things to do, actually.
你得另找時間了
Well, you'll have to rearrange them!
說起來你為什么來紐約
What are you doing in New York anyway?
我是來買生日禮物的
I came to buy a birthday present.
不能在倫敦買嗎
Couldn't you have done that in London?
買不到  世上只此一人養阿帕魯薩蒲絨絨
No, there's only one breeder of Appaloosa Puffskeins in the world
而他住在紐約  所以倫敦真買不到
and he lives in New York, so no.
抓了個違反3A條例的
I got a Section 3A.
順便告訴你  紐約不允許養神奇動物
By the way, we don't allow the breeding of magical creatures in New York.
一年前我們就讓那家伙關門大吉了
We closed that guy down a year ago.
嚴峻未知狀況
你好呀  戈德斯坦恩
Hey, Goldstein.
你好  雷德
Hey, Red.
-重案調查司  -你不是
- Major Investigation Department. - I thought you was...
重案調查司  抓了個違反3A條例的
Major Investigation Department! I got a Section 3A!
魔法造成的騷動
可能導致魔法世界暴露
國際巫師聯合會
The International Confederation
威脅說要派個審查團過來
is threatening to send a delegation.
他們認為此事與格林德沃在歐洲發動的襲擊有關
They think this is related to Grindelwald's attacks in Europe.
我就在現場  原因是神奇動物
I was there. This is a beast.
沒有人類有這么強的力量  會長女士
No human could do what this thing is capable of, Madam President.
無論這是什么  有一點毋庸置疑
Whatever it is, one thing's clear,
我們必須阻止它
it must be stopped.
它把麻雞們嚇壞了
It's terrorizing No-Majs
而麻雞們感到恐懼  他們會發動攻擊
and when No-Majs are afraid, they attack.
這可能會導致暴露  甚至是戰爭
This could mean exposure. It could mean war.
我已經說得很清楚了  戈德斯坦恩小姐
I made your position here quite clear, Miss Goldstein.
是的  會長女士  但我
Yes, Madam President, but I...
你不再是傲羅了
You are no longer an Auror.
-的確  會長女士  但  -戈德斯坦恩
- No, Madam President, but... - Goldstein.
出了個小事故
There's been a minor incident...
這間辦公室里的人正在操心一個大事故
Well, this office is currently concerned with very major incidents.
-出去  -遵命  夫人
- Get out. - Yes, ma'am.
魔杖許可辦公室
你辦魔杖許可證了嗎
So, you got your wand permit?
來紐約的外國人都得辦
All foreigners have to have them in New York.
幾周前我郵件申請了
I made a postal application weeks ago.
斯卡曼德  剛剛從赤道幾內亞過來的
Scamander... And you were just in Equatorial Guinea?
剛剛完成了一年的實地考察
I've just completed a year in the field.
我正在寫一本關于神奇動物的書
I'm writing a book about magical creatures.
是關于如何滅絕它們的指南嗎
Like... an extermination guide?
不是  是一本幫助大家理解
No. A guide to help people understand
我們為什么要保護這些動物
why we should be protecting these creatures
而不是殺了它們的指南
instead of killing them.
戈德斯坦恩  她人呢
Goldstein! Where is she?
去哪里的  戈德斯坦恩
Where is she? Goldstein!
戈德斯坦恩
Goldstein!
你剛剛又去插手調查隊的事了嗎
Did you just butt in on the Investigative Team again?
-你去哪了  -什么
- Where've you been? - What?
-她是在哪里遇見你的  -我
- Where'd she pick you up? - Me?
你又去跟蹤第二塞勒姆了嗎
Have you been tracking them Second Salemers again?
當然沒有  長官
Of course not, sir.
下午好  格雷夫斯先生  長官
Afternoon, Mr. Graves, sir!
下午好  阿伯內西
Afternoon, Abernathy.
格雷夫斯先生  長官  這是斯卡曼德先生
Mr. Graves, sir, this is Mr. Scamander.
他箱子里有個瘋狂的動物
He has a crazy creature in that case
跑掉了  在銀行引起了騷亂  長官
and it got out and caused mayhem in a bank, sir.
我們來看看那個小家伙吧
Let's see the little guy.
但是  長官...
But, sir...
蒂娜...
Tina...
對不起  奶奶
I'm sorry, Grandma.
我媽媽  你媽媽  去抓巫師啦
My momma, your momma, gonna catch a witch.
我媽媽  你媽媽  騎著掃帚飛
My momma, your momma, flying on a switch.
女巫就在我們之中  加入新塞勒姆軍團
我媽媽  你媽媽  女巫不哭呀
My momma, your momma, witches never cry.
我媽媽  你媽媽  女巫死光啦
My momma, your momma, witches gonna die!
一號女巫  河水淹死她
Witch number one, drown in a river!
二號女巫  繩子吊死她
Witch number two, gotta noose to give her!
三號女巫  大火燒死她
Witch number three, gonna watch her burn.
四號女巫  鞭子抽死她
Witch number four, flogging take a turn.
先去拿傳單  才能領食物  孩子們
Collect your leaflets before you get food, children.
那是個巫師標記嗎  夫人
Is it a witch's mark, ma'am?
不是  他很好
No. He's okay.
我簡直不敢相信你沒給他施一忘皆空
I can't believe you didn't obliviate that man!
假如有人問起來  我就完了
If there's an inquiry, I'm finished!
為什么是你完了  我才是那個
So why would you be finished? I'm the one that's...
我無權接近第二塞勒姆的
I'm not supposed to go near the Second Salemers!
那是什么
What was that?
蛾子  我覺得  大蛾子
Er... moth, I think. Big moth.
安靜  我在錄口供呢
Hey, quiet down. I'm trying to get a statement.
我告訴你這又是一起煤氣爆炸事故
I'm telling you it's a gas explosion again.
在徹底安全之前
I ain't taking the kids
我是不會帶孩子們上去的
back up there until it's safe.
抱歉  夫人  我們沒有聞到煤氣味
Sorry, ma'am. There ain't no smell of gas.
不是煤氣  警官  我看見了
It wasn't gas, Officer, I seen it!
那是個超級巨大的河馬  煤氣
It was a... gigantic... a huge hippopotto gas.
是煤氣
Gas.
我不知道
I don't know.
斯卡曼德先生
Mr. Scamander.
箱子被打開了
It was open?
只打開了一條縫
Just a smidge...
那只瘋狂的嗅嗅又跑出來了嗎
That crazy Niffler thing's on the loose again?
可能是吧
It might be.
那就快去找它啊
Then look for it!
看
Look!
他的脖子在流血  他受傷了
His neck's bleeding, he's hurt!
醒醒  麻雞先生
Wake up, Mr. No-Maj.
梅西·露易絲在上  那是什么東西
Mercy Lewis, what is that?
梅西·露易絲曾在塞勒姆時期指控她的鄰居會巫術
不必擔心  這是一只莫特拉鼠
Nothing to worry about. That is a Murtlap.
你那里面還裝了什么
What else have you got in there?
-是你  -你好啊
- You! - Hello.
悠著點  您是
Easy, Mr...
科瓦斯基  雅各布
Kowalski... Jacob.
你不能對他施一忘皆空
You can't obliviate him!
我們需要他當證人
We need him as a witness.
抱歉  但你剛剛還因為我
I'm sorry, you've just yelled at me the length
當時沒有對他施咒嘮叨了我半天啊
of New York for not doing it in the first place.
他受傷了  他看上去很不好
He's hurt! He looks ill!
他會沒事的
He'll be fine.
被莫特拉鼠咬了不嚴重的
Murtlap bites aren't serious.
我承認我還沒見過這么強烈的反應
I admit that is a slightly more severe reaction than I've seen,
但假如真的很嚴重  他會
but if it was really serious, he'd have...
怎樣
What?
首先的癥狀是從肛門噴出火花
Well, the first symptom would be flames out of his anus...
真是一團糟
This is balled up!
最多只會持續48小時
It'll last forty-eight hours at most!
-假如你愿意我可以帶著他  -帶著他
- I can keep him if you want me to. - Oh, keep him?
我們不能帶著他們
We don't keep them!
斯卡曼德先生
Mr. Scamander,
你對美國的巫師社群有任何的了解嗎
do you know anything about the wizarding community in America?
我確實略有耳聞
I do know a few things, actually.
我知道你們處理巫師和非魔法人士關系的
I know you have rather backwards laws
相關法律還比較落后
about relations with non-magic people.
你們不能和他們做朋友
That you're not meant to befriend them,
不能和他們結婚
that you can't marry them,
這在我看來有些可笑
which seems mildly absurd to me.
誰會愿意和他結婚啊
Who's going to marry him?
你倆都得跟我走
You're both coming with me.
我不明白為什么我也得跟著你
I don't see why I need to come with you.
-搭把手  -我是在做夢吧
- Help me! - I'm dreaming, right?
-拜托了  -沒錯  我累了
- Please. - Yeah, I'm tired,
我就沒去銀行
I never went to the bank.
這只是一場噩夢  對嗎
This is all just some big nightmare, right?
對我也是噩夢  科瓦斯基先生
For the both of us, Mr. Kowalski.
神奇魔法
這里就是新聞室了  來吧
And so this is the newsroom. Let's go.
你們好  給巴爾博恩一家讓路
Hey, how are you? Make way for the Barebones!
報紙正在進行所謂的上版備印
Now, they're just putting the papers to bed, as they say.
先生  肖先生正在和參議員談話
Mr. Shaw, sir, he's with the senator.
行了  巴克  我要見我父親
Never mind that, Barker, I wanna see my father!
很抱歉  肖先生  但您兒子堅持要進來
I'm so sorry, Mr. Shaw, but your son insisted.
父親  您一定不會想錯過這個的
Father, you're going to want to hear this.
我找到了個大新聞
I've got something huge!
你哥哥和我正忙著呢  蘭登
Your brother and I are busy here, Langdon.
在忙他競選的事
Working on his election campaign.
我們沒時間聽這個
We don't have time for this.
這位是瑪麗·盧·巴爾博恩
This is Mary Lou Barebone
她來自新塞勒姆慈善社
from the New Salem Preservation Society,
她給您帶來了個大新聞
and she's got a big story for you!
可不是嘛
Oh, she has, has she?
全市各處都發生了奇怪的事情
There's strange things going on all over the city.
造成這一切的人  他們和你我不同
The people behind this, they are not like you and me.
這是巫術  您看不出來嗎
This is witchcraft, don't you see.
-蘭登  -她不要報酬
- Langdon. - She doesn't want any money.
那么不是她的故事是假的
Then either her story is worthless,
就是她不要報酬的話是假的
or she's lying about the cost.
沒人會給你免費的午餐  蘭登
Nobody gives away anything valuable for free, Langdon.
您說的沒錯  肖先生
You are right, Mr. Shaw.
我們渴求遠比金錢更寶貴的東西
What we desire is infinitely more valuable than money.
您的影響力
It's your influence.
上百萬人訂閱您發行的報紙
Millions of people read your newspapers
得有人讓他們意識到面前的危機
and they need to be made aware about this danger.
地鐵災難事件  您看看照片就知道了
The crazy disturbances in the subway, just look at the pictures!
請你和你的朋友們馬上離開
I'd like you and your friends to leave.
不  你怎么就不明白
No, you're missing a trick here.
-睜眼看看這些事實  -鬧夠了嗎
- Just look at the evidence. - Really.
蘭登  聽父親的話  走吧
Langdon, just listen to Father and go. And...
把這些怪胎也一起帶走
Take the freaks with you.
-這是父親的辦公室  不是你的  -好吧
- This is Father's office, not yours. - Okay.
我實在受夠了  每次我一進來
And I'm sick of this every time I walk in here...
夠了  麻煩你們離開
That's it. Thank you.
希望您會改變主意  肖先生
We hope you'll reconsider, Mr. Shaw.
我們隨時等候您的消息
We're not difficult to find.
您不來  我們也很感謝您今天見我們
Until then, we thank you for your time.
小子
Hey, boy.
你東西掉了
You dropped something.
拿著  怪胎  扔進垃圾桶吧
Here you go, freak.
那里才是你們該呆的地方
Why don't you put that in the trash where you all belong.
右轉
Take a right here.
進屋之前我得申明
Okay, before we go in...
理論上我不能帶男士回家
I'm not supposed to have men on the premises.
既然如此  科瓦斯基先生和我完全可以去別處休息
In that case, Mr. Kowalski and I can easily seek other accommodation.
不行
Oh no, you don't!
當心腳下
Watch your step.
是你嗎  蒂娜
That you, Tina?
-是  埃斯波西托太太  -一個人嗎
- Yes, Mrs. Esposito! - Are you alone?
一如既往一個人  埃斯波西托太太
I'm always alone, Mrs. Esposito!
蒂妮  你帶了男人回來
Teenie, you brought men home?
兩位  這位是我妹妹
Gentlemen, this is my sister.
-加件衣服吧  奎妮  -當然
- You want to put something on, Queenie? - Sure.
-他們是誰  -這位是斯卡曼德先生
- So, who are they? - That's Mr. Scamander.
他犯下嚴重罪行
He's committed a serious
違反了《巫師保密法》
infraction of the National Statute of Secrecy.
他是個罪犯嗎
He's a criminal?
這位是科瓦斯基先生  是個麻雞
And this is Mr. Kowalski, he's a No-Maj.
麻雞
A No-Maj?
蒂妮  你要做什么
Teen, what are you up to?
他受傷了  說來話長
He's sick, it's a long story.
斯卡曼德先生丟了東西  我要幫他找回來
Mr. Scamander has lost something, I'm going to help him find it.
你得坐下親愛的  他一整天沒吃東西了
You need to sit down, honey. Hey, he hasn't eaten all day.
真可憐  銀行沒批準他開點心店的貸款
That's rough, he didn't get the money he wanted for his bakery.
你會做點心呀  親愛的
You bake, honey?
-我可喜歡做飯了  -你是攝神取念者
- I love to cook. - You're a Legilimens?
對啊  但碰上你們英國人就有些麻煩
Uh-huh, yeah. But I always have trouble with your kind. Brits.
因為口音的緣故
It's the accent.
-你會讀心術  -別擔心  親愛的
- You know how to read minds? - Don't worry, honey.
男人們第一次見到我跟你想法都一樣
Most guys think what you was thinking, first time they see me.
先給你做吃的
Now, you need food.
-又吃熱狗  -別對我使讀心術
- Hot dog... again? - Don't read my mind!
這午餐不怎么樣哦
Not a very wholesome lunch.
斯卡曼德先生
Hey, Mr. Scamander,
喜歡蘋果餡餅還是薄酥卷餅
you prefer pie or strudel?
我沒什么講究
I really don't have a preference.
你喜歡薄酥卷餅對吧  親愛的
You prefer strudel, huh, honey?
那就做卷餅
Strudel it is.
坐下吧  斯卡曼德先生
Well, sit down, Mr. Scamander.
不會毒死你的
We're not going to poison you.
你很難過
You're upset.
你母親又打你了嗎
It's your mother again.
有人說了什么  說了什么  告訴我
Somebody's said something, what did they say? Tell me.
-你覺得我是個怪胎嗎  -不
- Do you think I'm a freak? - No,
我認為你是一位非常特別的年輕人
I think you're a very special young man
否則我也不會請你協助我  對嗎
or I wouldn't have asked you to help me, would I?
-有消息了嗎  -我還在找
- Have you any news? - I'm still looking.
格雷夫斯先生  如果能知道性別
Mr. Graves, if I knew whether it was a girl or boy...
我只看到那孩子有巨大的力量
My vision showed only the child's immense power.
性別未知  但肯定不過十歲
He or she is no older than ten,
和你母親很親近
and I saw this child in close proximity to your mother.
你母親我看的真切
She I saw so plainly.
-這樣的人有好幾百  -還有一件事
- That could be any one of hundreds. - There is something else.
之前沒告訴你
Something I haven't told you.
我看到你與我在紐約并肩而立
I saw you beside me in New York.
只有你能獲取那孩子的信任
You're the one that gains this child's trust.
你是關鍵  我看到了
You are the key, I saw this.
你渴望加入魔法師的世界
You want to join the wizarding world.
我也是  克雷登斯  我渴望你能加入
I want those things too, Credence. I want them for you.
找到那個孩子  找到了我們就自由了
So find the child. Find the child and we'll all be free.
我的工作沒啥稀奇
The job ain't that glamorous.
整天沖泡咖啡
I mean, I spend most days making coffee,
用用讀心術  蒂娜才是職業女性
unjinxing the john. Tina's the career girl.
不  我們是孤兒
Nah. We're orphans.
父母在我們小時候得龍痘過世了
Ma and Pa died of dragon pox when we were kids.
你真貼心  我們倆相依為命也很好
You're sweet. But we got each other!
你能別一直對我用讀心術嗎
Could you stop reading my mind for a second?
別誤會  我很喜歡
Don't get me wrong, I love it.
這頓晚餐實在美味無比  我也是廚師
This meal, it's insanely good! This is what I do, I'm a cook.
但這是我今生今世吃過最美味的東西
And this is, like, the greatest meal I have ever had in my life.
你真迷人  我還是第一次認真和麻雞聊天呢
Oh, you slay me! I ain't never really talked to a No-Maj before.
真的嗎
Really?
我沒有在調情
I am not flirting!
我只是提醒你  別陷太深
I'm just saying, don't go getting attached,
最終要給他施遺忘咒的
he's going to have to be obliviated!
這是規矩
It's nothing personal.
-你還好嗎  親愛的  -戈德斯坦恩小姐
- Hey, you okay, honey? - Miss Goldstein,
我想科瓦斯基先生應該早點休息
I think Mr. Kowalski could do with an early night.
而且你和我明天也得早起
And besides, you and I will need to be up early tomorrow morning
去找我的嗅嗅  所以
to find my Niffler, so...
-嗅嗅是什么  -別問了
- What's a Niffler? - Don't ask.
你倆就在這兒加張床睡吧
Okay, you guys can bunk in here.
不知道你們想不想喝點熱乎的
I thought you might like a hot drink?
斯卡曼德先生  熱可可哎
Hey, Mr. Scamander... Look, cocoa!
-廁所在走廊盡頭右拐  -謝謝
- The toilet's down the hall to the right. - Thanks...
非常感謝
Very much.
來啊
Come on.
真是服了
For the love of...
好像有一個jesus
-坐下吧  -好主意
- Will you sit down? - Good idea.
肯定是莫特拉鼠咬的了
That's definitely the Murtlap.
你一定是易感體質
You must be particularly susceptible.
因為你是麻瓜  我們體質有些許不同
See, you're a Muggle. So our physiologies are subtly different.
別動  這藥能止汗
Stay still. Now that should stop the sweating.
這可以緩解痙攣
And one of those should sort the twitch.
拿好
Take that.
再來點
Come on...
-你在弄什么  -當地人管它叫蜷翼魔
- What you got there? - This the locals call Swooping Evil?
名字挺可怕  小家伙很敏捷
Not the friendliest of names. It's quite an agile fellow.
我正在研究它  我確信它的毒液
I've been studying him. And I am pretty sure his venom
合理稀釋后其實很有用
could be quite useful if properly diluted.
能消除痛苦的記憶
Just to remove bad memories, you know.
不過還是別在屋里放開它了
Probably shouldn't let him loose in here, though.
來吧
Come on.
來吧  下來吧
Come on. Down you come.
來
Come on.
感謝帕拉塞爾蘇斯
Oh, thank Paracelsus.
帕拉塞爾蘇斯  巧克力蛙卡片上出現過的人物
中世紀瑞士醫生  煉金術師  精通毒理學
要是你也跑出去那就天下大亂了
If you'd have got out that could have been quite catastrophic.
我來美國的真正原因就是為了它
You see, he's the real reason I came to America.
我想把弗蘭克帶回故鄉
To bring Frank home.
抱歉  別靠太近  他對陌生人有些敏感
No, sorry, stay there, he's a wee bit sensitive to strangers.
乖  乖  它被非法販賣了
Here you are, here you are. He was trafficked, you see.
我在埃及發現的它  全身綁著鎖鏈
I found him in Egypt, he was all chained up.
不忍心丟下它不管  我得帶它回家
Couldn't leave him there, had to bring him back.
帶你回歸屬之地  對不對  弗蘭克
I'm going to put you back where you belong, aren't I, Frank?
回到亞利桑那大荒野
To the wilds of Arizona.
它們來了
Here they come.
-誰來了  -角駝獸
- Here who comes? - The Graphorns.
沒事  沒事的
You're all right. You're all right.
你好  你們好
Hello, hello!
這是現存最后一對能哺育后代的角駝獸
So they're the last breeding pair in existence.
如果我沒救回它們
If I hadn't managed to rescue them,
角駝獸恐怕就從此滅絕了
that could have been the end of Graphorns, forever.
好啦
All right.
-你專門救治這些動物嗎  -沒錯
- What, you rescue these creatures? - Yes, that's right.
救治  養育  保護它們
Rescue, nurture, and protect them,
并試著慢慢給魔法師們灌輸他們的知識
and I'm gently trying to educate my fellow wizards about them.
跟我來
Come on.
泰特斯  芬  波比  馬洛  湯姆
Titus? Finn? Poppy, Marlow, Tom?
他感冒了  需要溫暖的身體
He had a cold. He needed some body warmth.
好了  回去吧
Right, on you hop.
他有些粘人  去吧  皮克特
See, he has some attachment issues. Now, come on, Pickett.
皮克特  他們不會欺負你的  回去吧
Pickett. No, they're not going to bully you. Now, come on.
皮克特
Pickett!
好吧  也難怪他們說我偏心了
All right. But that is exactly why they accuse me of favoritism.
杜戈爾去哪兒了
I wonder where Dougal's gone.
我來了  我來了  媽媽來了
All right, I'm coming, I'm coming, Mum's here. Mum's here.
-讓我瞧瞧  -我見過這些小家伙
- Hello, you, let me take a look at you. - I know these guys.
-你的鳥蛇  -你說我的鳥蛇
- Your Occamy. - You mean my Occamy?
是的  你想不想
Yes, do you want to...
好啊  當然好
Yeah, sure. Okay.
-你好  -抱歉  不要摸
- Hey. - No, sorry, don't pet them.
他們一出生就學會自我保護
They learn to defend themselves early.
因為蛋殼是銀的  非常值錢
See, their shells are made of silver so they're incredibly valuable.
-是嗎  -他們的巢總是慘遭獵殺洗劫
- Okay. - Their nests tend to get ransacked by hunters.
謝謝
Thank you.
-斯卡曼德先生  -叫我紐特吧
- Mr. Scamander? - Call me Newt.
紐特  我覺得我不是在做夢
Newt, I don't think I'm dreaming.
-怎么看出來的  -我可沒這想象力
- What gave it away? - I ain't got the brains to make this up.
不介意幫個忙吧
Actually, would you mind
把這些喂給那邊的月癡獸
throwing some of those pellets in with the Mooncalves over there?
-好的  -就在那邊
- Yeah, sure. - Just over there...
倒霉  嗅嗅跑了  就知道  搗蛋鬼
Bugger, Niffler's gone. Of course he has, little bugger.
不會放過任何閃亮亮的東西
Any chance to get his hands on something shiny.
今天干嘛了  雅各布
What did you do today, Jacob?
我去一個皮箱里玩了
I was inside a suitcase.
你們好  小家伙們  來吧  來吧
Hey. Hello, fellas. All right, all right.
慢慢吃  慢慢吃
Take it easy, take it easy.
真可愛  給你
Cutie. There it is.
-退后  -老天
- Step back. - Jeez...
-退后  -這是怎么回事
- Step back. - What's the matter with this?
-我說  退后  -知道了
- I said step away. - Yeah.
-這是什么鬼東西  -這是默默然
- What the hell is this thing? - It's an Obscurus.
我得出發了
I need to get going,
在跑掉的受傷前得趕緊找回來
find everyone who's escaped before they get hurt.
該擔心的真是他們嗎
Before they could get hurt?
沒錯  科瓦斯基先生  他們身處異鄉
Yes, Mr. Kowalski. They're currently in alien terrain,
四周圍繞著成千上萬
surrounded by millions
這個星球上最險惡的生物
of the most vicious creatures on the planet.
人類
Humans.
依你看來  一個中等體型
So where would you say that a medium-sized creature
喜歡開闊平原
that likes broad, open plains,
樹林和水坑的生物  她會去哪兒
trees, water holes, that kind of thing, where might she go?
在紐約市嗎
In New York City?
-對  -喜歡平原
- Yes. - Plains?
-中央公園  -在哪兒
- Central Park? - And where is that exactly?
你不知道中央公園在哪兒
Where is Central Park?
我是很樂意為你帶路
Well, look, I would come and show you,
但你不覺得有點對不起兩位女士嗎
but don't you think it's kind of a double cross?
人家收留我們  還給我們喝熱可可
The girls take us in, they make us hot cocoa.
你知道一旦你痊愈了
You do realize that when they see you've stopped sweating,
她們轉眼就會對你施遺忘咒對吧
they'll obliviate you in a heartbeat.
什么是遺忘咒
What does obliviate Mean?
就像夢醒  關于魔法的記憶消失不見
It'll be like you wake up and all memory of magic is gone.
-這一切我都會忘掉嗎  -沒錯
- I won't remember any of this? - No.
好吧  我幫你
All right, yeah, okay, I'll help you.
那走吧
Come on, then.
克雷登斯  你去哪兒了
Credence, where have you been?
我在找明天集會的場地
I was looking for a place for tomorrow's meeting.
32街上有塊地方我們可以
There's a corner on Thirty-Second Street that could...
對不起  媽媽  我沒注意到這么晚了
I'm sorry, Ma. I didn't realize it was so late.
-晚飯時我在觀察你  -然后呢
- I was watching you at dinner. - Yeah.
你很討人喜歡  對吧  科瓦斯基先生
People like you, don't they, Mr. Kowalski?
你肯定也很討人喜歡
Well, I'm sure people like you too.
不  我總是討人嫌
No, not really. I annoy people.
你為什么要做點心師呢
Why did you decide to be a baker?
因為我在罐頭廠呆的快要窒息了
Well, because I'm dying in that canning factory.
那的人都是行尸走肉
Everyone there's dying.
那里能活生生把你的意志榨干
It just crushes the life outta you.
-你喜歡罐頭食品嗎  -不喜歡
- You like canned food? - No.
我也不喜歡  所以我想做手工點心
Yeah. Me neither. That's why I want to make pastries, you know.
吃點心讓人開心  這邊走
It makes people happy. We're going this way.
那你拿到貸款了嗎
So did you get your loan?
沒  我沒東西作抵押
No, I ain't got no collateral.
或許是在部隊呆太久了  誰知道呢
Stayed in the army too long, apparently, I don't know.
-你打過仗嗎  -當然打過
- You fought in the war? - Of course I fought in the war,
人人都打過仗  你難道沒有嗎
everyone fought in the war. You didn't fight in the war?
我主要和龍打交道  烏克蘭鐵腹龍
I worked mostly with dragons, Ukrainian Ironbellies,
東線戰場
Eastern Front.
玻璃破碎
Finestra.
速速飛來
Accio!
這下高興了
All right? Happy?
找到一個  還剩倆
One down, two to go.
-犯人朝那跑了  警官  -舉起手來
- They went that way, Officer. - Hands up!
那是什么
What the hell is that?
獅子
Lion...
紐約比我想象中好玩多了
You know, New York is considerably more interesting than I'd expected.
戴上
Put this on.
我為什么需要戴這種東西
Why would I have to wear something like this?
因為你的腦袋
Because your skull is
在巨大沖擊之下很容易開花
susceptible to breakage under immense force.
但我們還給他們做了熱可可呢
But we made them cocoa.
好了
Right.
-不如把這也穿上吧  -好的
- Okay, if you just, pop this on. - Okay.
這下真的沒啥可擔心的了
Now, there's absolutely nothing for you to worry about.
你說不用擔心時
Tell me, has anyone ever
真的有人相信你過嗎
believed you when you told them not to worry?
我始終認為  擔心就是雙重遭罪
My philosophy is that worrying means you suffer twice.
季節到了  她需要交配
She's in season. She needs to mate.
毒角獸麝香  對她最有吸引力
Erumpent musk, she is mad for it.
好姑娘
Good girl...
來吧  到箱子里去
Come on, into the case.
討厭
Get...
糟糕
Oh, no.
修復如初
Repar...
梅林的胡子啊
Merlin's beard!
這兩根一模一樣
They're exactly the same.
-一模一樣  -紐特
- Same thing. - Newt!
別  別
No, no, no, don't!
非常抱歉
I'm so sorry.
干得漂亮  科瓦斯基先生
Good show, Mr. Kowalski!
叫我雅各布吧
Call me Jacob.
抓了倆  還剩一個
Two down, one to go.
你先進吧
In you hop.
女士們先生們
Ladies and gentlemen,
今晚的主要發言人
tonight's keynote speaker,
無需我過多介紹
needs no introduction from me.
肖
美國的未來
他被譽為未來的總統
He's been mentioned as a future president.
不信的話
And if you don't believe me,
看看他父親的報紙就知道了
just read his daddy's newspapers.
女士們先生們
Ladies and gentlemen,
讓我隆重為你們介紹紐約的參議員
I'll give you the senator for New York,
亨利·肖
Henry Shaw!
謝謝您
Thank you.
謝謝大家
Thank you!
謝謝
Thank you.
某些方面我們的確取得了不小的進步
And it's true we have made some progress,
但游手好閑是不可能有回報的
but there is no reward for idleness.
當那些烏煙瘴氣的酒吧被取締之后
So just as the odious saloons have been banished...
此時為1926年
正處于美國禁酒令時期
出什么事了
What's going on?
至于那些釀酒廠
So now the pool halls,
和私人作坊
and these private parlors...
那是什么
What is that?
女巫
Witches!
嚴峻未知狀況
高度緊急
美國魔法國會
我們的美國同僚
Our American friends have
對有人違背了《保密法》視而不見
permitted a breach of the Statute of Secrecy,
使整個魔法世界面臨暴露的威脅
that threatens to expose us all.
我不想聽
I will not be lectured by the man
眼睜睜放走了蓋勒特·格林德沃的人
who let Gellert Grindelwald
來教訓我
slip through his fingers.
會長女士  很抱歉打擾您
Madam President, I'm so sorry to interrupt,
但這事十萬火急
but this is critical.
你這樣魯莽的擅自闖入
You'd better have an excellent
最好有個合理理由  戈德斯坦恩小姐
excuse for this intrusion, Miss Goldstein.
是的  我有
Yes, I do.
女士  昨天一個帶手提箱的巫師來了紐約
Madam. Yesterday a wizard entered New York with a case.
箱子里全是神奇生物
This case full of magical creatures,
很不幸的是  有一些逃脫了
and unfortunately, some have escaped.
他昨天到的嗎
He arrived yesterday?
你24小時前就知道
You have known for twenty-four hours
一個未登記的巫師在紐約放跑了魔法生物
that an unregistered wizard set magical beasts loose in New York.
卻等到有人遇害了才告訴我們嗎
and you see fit to tell us only when a man has been killed?
-誰被殺了  -他在哪
- Who has been killed? - Where is this man?
斯卡曼德
Scamander?
您好  部長大人
Hello, Minister.
忒修斯·斯卡曼德  那個一戰英雄
Theseus Scamander? The war hero?
不  這是他弟弟
No, this is his little brother.
你來紐約干什么
And what are you doing in New York?
-買阿帕魯薩蒲絨絨  先生  -我信了
- I came to buy an Appaloosa Puffskein, sir.- Right.
你來這里真正的目的是什么
What are you really doing here?
戈德斯坦恩  這又是誰
Goldstein, and who is this?
他叫雅各布·科瓦斯基  會長女士
This is Jacob Kowalski, Madam President,
他是被斯卡曼德先生的動物咬了的麻雞
he's a No-Maj who got bitten by one of Mr. Scamander's creatures.
-麻雞  -施遺忘咒了嗎
- No-Maj? - Obliviated?
抹掉他的記憶
Obliviate him!
梅林的胡子啊
Merlin's beard.
您知道您的哪只動物該為此負責嗎
You know which of your creatures was responsible,
斯卡曼德先生
Mr. Scamander?
這不是動物干的
No creature did this.
別裝了
Don't pretend!
你們知道那是什么  看傷痕就知道
You must know what that was, look at the marks...
這是默默然干的
That was an Obscurus.
滿口胡言  斯卡曼德先生
You go too far, Mr. Scamander.
在美國絕對沒有默默然
There is no Obscurial in America.
扣押他的箱子  格雷夫斯
Impound that case, Graves!
-等等  別  還給我  -逮捕他們
- Wait. No. Give that back. - Arrest them!
別傷害那些動物
Don't hurt those creatures.
求您了  您不理解
Please, you don't understand,
他們都不危險的  都不危險
nothing in there is dangerous, nothing!
我們自會判斷  押他們去監獄
We'll be the judges of that! Take them to the cells!
別傷害這些動物  他們都不危險的
Don't hurt those creatures, nothing in there is dangerous!
求您了  別傷害我的動物們
Please, don't hurt my creatures!
他們不危險的  求您了  不危險的
They aren't dangerous! Please, they are not dangerous!
他們不會傷害人的
They are not dangerous!
關于你的動物我很抱歉  斯卡曼德先生
I am so sorry about your creatures, Mr. Scamander.
真的
I truly am.
誰能告訴我
Can someone please tell me
這個默然者還是默默然到底是什么
what this Obscurial or Obscurus thing is? Please?
幾百年都沒有出現過了
There hasn't been one for centuries.
三個月前我在蘇丹遇到了一個
I met one in Sudan three months ago.
雖然以前更多  但現在也還有
There used to be more of them but they still exist.
那時巫師們還未隱遁
Before wizards went underground,
我們還在被麻瓜們追殺
when we were still being hunted by Muggles,
有時為了逃脫厄運
young wizards and witches
年輕的巫師們會抑制自己的魔法力量
sometimes tried to suppress their magic to avoid persecution.
但他們并未學會駕馭和控制他們的力量
Instead of learning to harness or to control their powers,
反而衍生了所謂的默默然
they developed what was called an Obscurus.
這是種極不穩定  難以控制的黑魔法
It's an unstable, uncontrollable Dark force
會脫離宿主然后攻擊他人
that busts out and attacks...
之后便消失得無影無蹤
and then vanishes.
默然者活不久的  對吧
Obscurials can't survive long, can they?
沒有任何案例表明
There's no documented case
默然者能活過十歲
of any Obscurial surviving past the age of ten.
我在非洲遇到的小女孩當時才...
The one I met in Africa was eight when she...
她離世時才八歲
She was eight when she died.
所以你們的意思是
What are you telling me here,
參議員肖是被一個小孩殺死的
that Senator Shaw was killed by a kid?
我媽媽  你媽媽  騎著掃帚飛
My momma, your momma, flying on a switch.
我媽媽  你媽媽  女巫不哭呀
My momma, your momma, witches never cry.
我媽媽  你媽媽  女巫死光啦
My momma, your momma, witches gonna die!
第一個女巫  河水淹死她
Witch number one, drown in a river!
第二個女巫  繩子吊死她
Witch number two, gotta noose to give her!
-該發傳單了  -第三個女巫
- Hand out your leaflets! - Witch number three...
你們扔掉的話我會知道的
I'll know if you dump them.
看到可疑的東西記得告訴我
Tell me if you see anything suspicious.
能認識你很高興  雅各布
It was good to make your acquaintance,Jacob
希望你的點心屋能夠順利開張
and I hope you get your bakery.
您很有意思  斯卡曼德先生
You're an interesting man, Mr. Scamander.
格雷夫斯先生
Mr. Graves...
當年因威脅他人生命被霍格沃茨開除
You were thrown out of Hogwarts for endangering human life...
-那是個意外  -還是動物引起的吧
- That was an accident! - With a beast.
然而你的一位老師強烈反對開除你
Yet one of your teachers argued strongly against your expulsion.
現在走到了這步田地
And now...
阿不思·鄧布利多為什么這么喜歡你
What makes Albus Dumbledore so fond of you?
鄧布利多曾擔任變形課教授
我真的不知道
I really couldn't say.
所以在這里放出一只危險的生物
So setting a pack of dangerous creatures loose here was...
也是一場意外  是嗎
Was just another accident, is that right?
我故意這么做能有什么好處
Why would I do it deliberately?
能曝光巫師世界
To expose wizardkind.
挑起魔法世界和人類世界的戰爭
To provoke war between the magical and non-magical worlds.
你的意思是以大屠殺來成全大局嗎
Mass slaughter for the greater good, you mean?
格林德沃信徒的口號
是的  就這個意思
Yes. Quite.
我不是格林德沃的信徒  格雷夫斯先生
I'm not one of Grindelwald's fanatics, Mr. Graves.
關于這個你有什么話說  斯卡曼德先生
I wonder what you can tell me about this, Mr. Scamander?
這是只默默然  但不是你想的那樣
It's an Obscurus. But it's not what you think so.
救那個蘇丹女孩的時候
I managed to separate it from the Sudanese girl
我試著把它分離了出來
from the Sudanese girl as I tried to save her.
我只想帶回家做研究
Wanted to take it home, to study it.
但離開標本泡它是無法存活的
But it cannot survive outside that,
它無法傷害任何人了  蒂娜
it could not hurt anyone, Tina!
所以離了宿主這東西就沒用了
So it's useless without the host?
"沒用了"  "沒用了"
"Useless?" "Useless?"
能致一個孩子于死地的寄生魔法力量
That is a parasitical magical force that killed a child.
你覺得它能有什么用
What on earth would you use it for?
你騙不了任何人  斯卡曼德先生
You fool nobody, Mr. Scamander.
你把默默然帶到紐約來
You brought this Obscurus into the
就是希望進行大規模屠殺
city of New York in the hope of causing mass disruption,
破壞《保密法》  曝光巫師世界
breaking the Statute of Secrecy and revealing the magical world.
你知道它不能傷人的  你明明知道
You know that can't hurt anyone, you know that!
你將以背叛巫師同胞的罪名
You are therefore guilty of a treasonous betrayal
被處以死刑
of your fellow wizards and are sentenced to death.
戈德斯坦恩小姐作為煽動你的同黨
Miss Goldstein, who has aided and abetted you...
不  她什么都沒做
No, she's done nothing of the kind.
處以同等刑法
She receives the same sentence.
趕緊動手吧
Just do it immediately.
-我會親自通知皮奎里會長的  -蒂娜
- I will inform President Picquery myself. - Tina.
麻煩了
Please.
別這么做  貝娜黛特  求你了
Don't do this, Bernadette, please...
不會疼的
It don't hurt.
-蒂娜  -媽媽  -蒂娜
- Tina... - Momma... - Tina...
來吧小南瓜  該睡覺啦  準備好了嗎
Come on, pumpkin, time for bed. Are you ready?
看上去是不是很美好
Don't that look good?
想進去吧
You wanna get in?
-山姆  -奎妮
- Hey, Sam! - Hey, Queenie.
他們叫你去樓下
They need you downstairs.
-我來施遺忘咒  -你無權執行
- I'll obliviate this guy. - You ain't qualified.
山姆
Hey, Sam.
西西里知道你在和露比幽會嗎
Does Cecily know you been seeing Ruby?
-你是怎么  -只要讓我施咒
- How'd you... - Let me obliviate this guy
我保證一個字也不會往外說
and she'll never hear about it from me.
你干什么
What are you doing?
蒂妮有麻煩了  我正在四處傾聽
Teen's in trouble, I'm trying to listen...
雅各布  紐特的手提箱在哪里
Jacob, where's Newt's case?
應該是那個格雷夫斯拿走了
I think that guy Graves took it.
好吧  跟我來
Okay, come on.
你不打算抹掉我的記憶嗎
What? You're not gonna obliviate me?
當然不會了  你跟我們是一伙兒的
Of course not, you're one of us now!
沒事了
It's okay.
阿拉霍洞開
Alohomora.
芝麻開門
Aberto...
他應該是用更高級的咒語鎖了門
He would know a fancy spell to lock his office.
好了  現在來看看你的美好回憶吧
Okay, let's get the good stuff out of you.
女巫
Witch!
-它會吃掉我的  -別慌
- It's just gonna eat me! - Don't panic!
我不慌還能怎么辦
What do you suggest I do instead?
跳過來
Jump.
-瘋了嗎你  -跳到它背上
- Are you crazy? - Jump on him.
蒂娜  聽我說  我會接住你的
Tina, listen to me. I'll catch you.
蒂娜
Tina!
我會接住你的
I'll catch you.
有我在  蒂娜  跳
I've got you, Tina. Go!
快走
Come on!
馬上就來
Coming through!
讓開
Move!
別吃他的腦子  快走吧
Leave his brains, come on!
快
Come on!
-那是什么  -蜷翼魔
- What is that thing? - Swooping Evil.
我愛死它了
Well, I love it!
進去吧
Get in.
奎妮
Queenie!
你這是要去哪
Where you going?
我生病了  阿伯內西先生
I'm sick, Mr. Abernathy.
又病了啊
Again?
你手里提的是什么
Well, what've you got there?
女士用品
Ladies things.
你要看一下嗎  我不介意的
You wanna take a look? I don't mind.
噢老天  不用了  我
Good gravy, no! I...
-希望你早日康復  -謝謝你
- You get well now! - Thanks.
克雷登斯  你找到那個孩子了嗎
Credence. Have you found the child?
我做不到
I can't.
我看看
Show me.
我的孩子  我們越早找到這個孩子
My boy, the sooner we find this child,
你便能越快地脫離痛苦
the sooner you can put that pain in the past where it belongs.
我想把這個送給你  克雷登斯
I want you to have this, Credence.
能讓我放心托付它的人不多
I would trust very few with it.
很少
Very few.
可是你
But you...
你跟別人不一樣
You're different.
只要找到了那個孩子
When you find the child,
碰一下這個標識我便知道  我會來找你
touch this symbol and I will know, and I will come to you.
事成之后   你將在巫師界
Do this and you will be honored among wizards.
名垂千古
Forever.
這孩子快不行了了  克雷登斯
The child is dying, Credence.
時間緊迫
Time is running out.
你祖父養鴿子啊  我祖父養貓頭鷹
Your grandfather kept pigeons? Mine bred owls.
我以前很喜歡給他們喂食來著
I used to love feeding them.
格雷夫斯一直說最近的混亂是動物引起的
Graves always insisted the disturbances were caused by a beast.
我們得盡早把你的動物找回來
We need to catch all your creatures
這樣他就不能拿它們當擋箭牌了
so he can't keep using them as a scapegoat.
還剩一只沒找到
There's only one still missing.
杜戈爾  我的隱形獸
Dougal, my Demiguise.
你還給它起了名字
Dougal?
稍微有點棘手的是
Slight problem is that...
它是隱形的
He's invisible.
-隱形的  -對  大部分時間里
- Invisible? - Yes, most of the time... He does...
-會隱形的東西還怎么抓  -難上加難
- How do you catch something that...? - With immense difficulty.
-納爾拉克  -你說什么
- Gnarlak! - Excuse me?
納爾拉克  我還是傲羅時他是我的線人
Gnarlak, he was an informant of mine when I was an Auror!
他曾暗地里進行魔法生物的買賣
He used to trade in magical creatures on the side.
他不會恰好對追蹤腳印感興趣吧
He wouldn't happen to have an interest in paw prints, would he?
一切能賣的東西他都感興趣
He's interested in anything he can sell.
*當巨龍擄走他心愛的女孩*
*When the dragon snapped up his best girl*
歌曲為《Blind Pig》  歌詞也為J.K.羅琳所寫
*比利威格蟲也忘記回旋*
*And the Billywig forgot to twirl*
源自澳大利亞的魔法生物
飛行時身體會回旋
影片前半部分出現的蘿卜形狀的藍色小蟲
*愛人離開  留他獨自寒心徹骨*
*When his sweetheart left him cold*
*獨角獸也斷了長角*
*And the unicorn done lost his horn*
這酒吧要怎么點單啊
How do I get a drink in this joint?
干嘛  沒見過家養小精靈嗎
What? Ain't you ever seen a house-elf before?
不  當然不是  我愛死家養小精靈了
No, no, of course I have. I love house-elves.
家養小精靈為巫師家庭中地位最卑賤的物種
因此被巫師所厭惡
我的叔叔就是個家養小精靈
My uncle's a house-elf.
我看也是
Yeah...
六小杯咯咯酒和一杯大腦沖擊波  謝謝
Six shots of gigglewater and a lobe blaster, please.
1731年起風靡美國巫師界的一種雞尾酒
喝了會讓人咯咯咯地發笑
所有的麻雞都像你一樣嗎
Are all No-Majs like you?
不 只有我像我一樣
No, I'm the only one like me.
通緝令
耶利米亞·沃德沃特
綁架殺害麻雞
這里一半的人都被我抓過
I've arrested half of the people in here.
你可以說我多管閑事  但是
You can tell me to mind my own business, but...
但在死亡池里我看到了一些東西
I saw something in that death potion back there.
我看到你抱住了那個第二塞勒姆的男孩
I saw you hugging that Second Salem boy.
他叫克雷登斯
His name's Credence.
他媽媽虐待他
His mother beats him.
她鞭打她收養的所有小孩
She beats all those kids she adopted,
但似乎對他下手最重
but she seems to hit him the most.
她就是你攻擊的那個麻雞嗎
And she was the No-Maj you attacked?
我就是這樣失業的
That's how I lost my job.
我動手時正是她和信徒的集會
I went for her in front of a meeting of her crazy followers.
在場的人都必須被抹去記憶
They all had to be obliviated.
當時惹了很大的亂子
It was a big scandal.
他來了
It's him.
所以...
So...
你就是那個提了一箱子神奇動物的人吧
You're the guy with the case full of monsters, huh?
消息傳得挺快嘛
News travels fast.
我希望您能告訴我
I was hoping you'd be able
有沒有什么奇異的事發生
to tell me if there have been any sightings.
或者蹤跡之類
Tracks. That sort of thing.
你的腦袋值不少錢呢  斯卡曼德先生
You've got a big price on your head, Mr. Scamander.
我為什么要幫你  不如把你交上去
Why should I help you instead of turning you in?
看來您的消息不免費啊
I take it I'll have to make it worth your while?
你就當是封口費吧
Let's consider it a cover charge.
魔法國會的懸賞可比這多多了
MACUSA's offering more than that.
望月鏡
Lunascope?
我有五個
I got five.
冰凍的火灰蛇蛋
Frozen Ashwinder egg.
現在我們...
You see, now we're...
等一下
Wait a minute.
那是護...  那是護樹羅鍋吧
That's Bow... That's a Bowtruckle, right?
不行
No.
得了吧  它們能開鎖對吧
Come on. They pick locks, am I right?
我不賣
You're not having him.
希望你能從魔法國會的
Good luck getting back alive, Mr. Scamander,
漫天抓捕中逃生  斯卡曼德先生
what with the whole of MACUSA on your back.
成交
All right.
皮克特...
Pickett...
有個隱形的家伙在第五大道搞破壞
Something invisible's been wreaking havoc around Fifth Avenue.
你們可以去梅西百貨商場看看
You may wanna check out Macy's department store.
也許是你們要找的東西
Might help with what you're looking for.
杜戈爾
Dougal.
最后一件事
One last thing.
魔法國會里有位格雷夫斯先生
There's a Mr. Graves who works at MACUSA.
不知道你了不了解他的背景
I was wondering what you knew of his background.
你問題可真多
You ask a lot of questions,
斯卡曼德先生
Mr. Scamander.
好奇害死貓
That can get you killed.
魔法國會的人來了
MACUSA are coming!
你竟敢泄密
You tipped them off!
懸賞
抱歉了  納爾拉克先生
Sorry, Mr. Gnarlak...
看到他就讓我想起我的工頭
Reminds me of my foreman!
你在做什么  克雷登斯
What are you doin? Credence?
你在哪找到的這個
Where'd you get this?
還給我  克雷登斯  那只是個玩具
Give it back, Credence. It's just a toy!
怎么回事
What is this?
把它給我
Take it off!
-媽  -我不是你媽
- Ma... - I am not your Ma!
你媽是個邪惡的  不正常的女人
Your mother was a wicked, unnatural woman!
-那是我的  -莫德絲蒂
- It was mine. - Modesty...
怎么回事
What is this?
盡管隱形獸平時性情溫和
So Demiguises are fundamentally peaceful,
但被惹怒了也是會咬人的
but they can give a nasty nip if provoked.
你們倆  去那邊
You two, head that way.
盡力隱藏自己的目的
And try very hard not to be predictable.
那是隱形獸嗎
Was that the Demiguise?
不  但我覺得那是隱形獸來這兒的目的
No, I think it might be the reason that the Demiguise is here.
它的視線能自動分析可能性
Its sight operates on probability,
所以它能預測到很近的未來
so it can foresee the most likely immediate future.
-那它是做什么的  -照顧孩子
- So what's it doing? - It's babysitting.
-你說什么  -這是我的錯
- What did you just say? - This is my fault.
我以為全找回來了
I thought I had them all,
可我數漏了一個
but I must have miscounted.
它是在照顧那玩意兒
It was babysitting that?
鳥蛇可以隨意改變體型
Occamies are choranaptyxic.
可以變大到塞滿所在的整個空間
So they grow to fill available space.
媽媽來了
Mummy's here.
我們需要只昆蟲
We need an insect,
什么蟲子都行  還要一個茶壺
any kind of insect and a teapot!
快找個茶壺來
Find a teapot!
抓到了  抓到了
I got it. I got it!
茶壺
Teapot!
把蟑螂放茶壺里
Roach in teapot...
隨意變形
Choranaptyxic.
它們也可以縮身來適應空間
They also shrink to fit the available space.
告訴我真相
Tell me the truth.
現在逃掉的
Was that everything that
-真的都找到了嗎  -都找到了
- came out of the case? - That's everything.
這句是真話
And that's the truth.
-她來了  -回家高興嗎
- Here she comes. - Happy to be home?
我打賭你一定累了  伙計
Bet you're exhausted, buddy.
來吧  就在這兒
Come on. There you go, that's right.
沒錯  我們是得談談
Right. I think we need to talk.
我不會讓真讓他帶走你的  皮克特
I wouldn't have let him keep you, Pickett.
皮克  我寧愿失去手也不會拋棄你的
Pick, I would rather chop off my hand than get rid of you.
你為了付出了那么多  相信我吧
After everything you have done for me, now come on.
皮克  不是說好不生悶氣的嗎
Pick, we've talked about sulking before, haven't we?
皮克特
Pickett...
求你了  給我個微笑
Come on, give me a smile.
皮克特  給我
Pickett, give me a...
好吧  你平時絕對沒這么小氣
All right. Now, that is beneath you.
紐特
Newt.
-她是誰  -誰也不是
- Who is she? - That's no one.
麗塔·萊斯特蘭奇
Leta Lestrange?
我聽說過他們一家
I've heard of that family.
他們不都有點...你懂的
Aren't they kinda, you know?
請別讀我的心
Please don't read my mind.
對不起  我說過別讀了
Sorry, I asked you not to.
我知道  抱歉
I know, I'm sorry.
我就是控制不住
I can't help it.
每當人們傷心時
People are easiest to
-最容易被讀心  -我不傷心
- read when they're hurting. - I'm not hurting.
總之  事情已經過去很久了
Anyway, it was a long time ago.
你們在學校的友誼真的很親密
That was a real close friendship you had at school.
我們倆都不怎么適合學校生活
Neither of us really fitted in at school.
-所以我倆就變成了  -變成了摯友
- So we became quite... - You became real close.
那么多年
For years.
她只會索取  你需要也能為你付出的人
She was a taker. You need a giver.
-你們在聊些什么  -沒什么
- What are you two talking about? - Nothing.
-學校的事  -對  學校
- School. - School.
你們剛才說學校  這兒還有學校嗎
Did you say school? Is there a school?
巫師學校  就在美國
A wizardry school here? In America?
那當然  伊法魔尼
Of course, Ilvermorny!
它可是全球最棒的魔法學校
It's only the best wizard school in the whole world!
我想你會發現  世界上
I think you'll find the best
最好的魔法學校是霍格沃茨
wizarding school in the world is Hogwarts!
廢話多
Hogwash!
危險
Danger.
他能感覺到危險
He senses danger.
默然者來了
The Obscurial was here?
她去哪了
Where did she go?
救救我  救救我
Help me. Help me.
你不是說你還有個妹妹嗎
Didn't you tell me you had another sister?
求你救救我
Please help me.
你妹妹在哪
Where's your other sister,
-克雷登斯 -求你救救我
- Credence? - Please, help me.
-你的小妹妹  她去哪了  -求你了
- The little one? Where did she go? - Please...
你妹妹現在很危險
Your sister's in grave danger.
我們得找到她
We need to find her.
-這是哪  -媽媽在這里收養了她
- What is this place? - Ma adopted Modesty out of here.
她家里當時有十二個人
From a family of twelve.
她很想念他的兄弟姐妹
She misses her brothers and sisters.
時常提起他們
She still talks about them.
她現在在哪
Where is she?
我不知道
I don't know.
你是個聰明人  克雷登斯
You're a Squib, Credence.
從我第一次遇見你  我就知道
I could smell it off you the minute I met you.
什么
What?
你有魔法血統  可你無法施展
You have magical ancestry, but no power.
你說過你會教我
But you said you could teach me.
這只能你自己琢磨
You're unteachable.
你母親的死  就是對你的獎賞
Your mother's dead. That's your reward.
我受夠你了
I'm done with you.
莫德絲蒂
Modesty?
Modesty.
不必害怕
There's no need to be afraid.
有我和你哥哥克雷登斯在
I'm here with your brother, Credence.
出來吧
Out you come, now.
克雷登斯  我得向你道歉
Credence, I owe you an apology.
我信任了你
I trusted you.
我以為你是我朋友  以為你不一樣
I thought you were my friend. That you were different.
你能控制住它  克雷登斯
You can control it, Credence.
可是我并不想  格雷夫斯先生
But I don't think I want to, Mr. Graves.
天哪  是那個什么默然者嗎
Jeez. Is that the Obscuriathing?
它比我聽說過的所有默然者都強悍
That's more powerful than any Obscurial I have ever heard of.
如果我沒能回來  幫我照顧好它們
If I don't come back, look after my creatures.
所有需要知道的都記錄在這了
Everything that you need to know is in there.
什么
What?
他們殺不了他
They're not killing it.
紐特  你聽到了  照顧好它們
Newt! You heard him, look after them!
-親愛的  拿好了  -不不不
- Keep holda that, honey. - No, no, no!
我不能帶上你  讓我走吧  雅各布
I can't take you. Please let go of me, Jacob!
你說過我們是一伙兒的
You're the one that said I was one of youse,
-對吧  -這太危險了
- right? - It's too dangerous.
被它寄生你居然幸存到現在  克雷登斯
To survive so long, with this inside you, Credence,
這就是奇跡  你就是個奇跡
is a miracle. You are a miracle.
跟我走吧  想想我們倆聯手能做多少
Come with me, think of what we could achieve together.
紐特
Newt!
是第二塞勒姆的那個男孩
It's the Second Salem boy.
他才是默然者
He's the Obscurial.
但他不是孩子了
He's not a child.
肯定是他的魔力太強大
His power must be so strong,
不知怎么幸存了下來
he's somehow managed to survive.
紐特  一定要救下他
Newt! Save him.
格雷夫斯先生
Mr. Graves.
蒂娜  你總是出現在最不該出現的地方
Tina. You're always turning up where you are least wanted.
控制住他  否則我們一旦暴露
Contain this, or we are exposed
便會爆發戰爭
and it will mean war.
克雷登斯
Credence!
克雷登斯  我能幫你
Credence, I can help you.
-封鎖這里  -是  長官
- Bar the area. - Yes, sir.
不允許任何人進來
I don't want anyone else down there!
克雷登斯
Credence...
你叫克雷登斯  對吧
It's Credence, isn't it?
我是來幫助你的  克雷登斯
I'm here to help you, Credence.
我不是來傷害你的
I'm not here to hurt you.
我見過和你一樣的人
I've met someone just like you,
克雷登斯
Credence.
一個女孩
A girl.
一個被囚禁的小女孩
A young girl who'd been imprisoned,
她因為有魔法
she had been locked away
被關了起來  還受到折磨
and she'd been punished for her magic.
克雷登斯
Credence...
我能過你那兒去嗎
Can I come over to you?
我能過去嗎
Can I come over?
那東西殺了我兒子  我要討個公道
That thing killed my son. I want justice!
我要揭露你的真面目以及你的所作所為
I'll expose you for who you are and what you've done.
快看  拍  拍照
Look! Take... Take photos.
克雷登斯
Credence.
克雷登斯  不要
Credence, no!
別這樣做  求你了
Don't do this. Please.
接著說  蒂娜
Keep talking, Tina.
繼續說話  他會聽你的  他在聽
Keep talking to him, he'll listen to you. He's listening.
我知道那個女人對你做了些什么
I know what that woman did to you.
我知道你備受煎熬
I know that you've suffered.
你不能再這樣下去了
You need to stop this now.
我和紐特會保護你的
Newt and I will protect you.
這個男人  他在利用你
This man... He is using you.
別聽她的  克雷登斯
Don't listen to her, Credence.
我是想給你自由
I want you to be free.
-沒事的  -這就對了
- It's all right. - That's it.
-別  你們會嚇到他的  -放下魔杖
- Don't, you'll frighten him. - Wands down!
敢傷他的人我要他好看  克雷登斯
Anyone harms him, they'll answer to me. Credence!
克雷登斯
Credence...
-不  -不
- No. - No!
克雷登斯  你們這些傻子
Credence... You fools.
知道你們做了什么嗎
Do you realize what you've done?
殺死默然者是我的命令
The Obscurial was killed on my orders,
-格雷夫斯先生  -是啊
- Mr. Graves. - Yes.
這一點歷史不會忘記的  會長女士
And history will surely note that, Madam President.
今晚在這里發生的事不公道
What was done here tonight was not right!
是他殺死了那個麻雞
He was responsible for the death of a No-Maj.
他帶來了暴露我們的危險
He risked the exposure of our community.
他違反了我們最神圣的法律
He has broken one of our most sacred laws.
讓我們像水溝里的老鼠般躲藏的法律
A law that has us scuttling like rats in the gutter!
迫使我們壓抑本性的法律
A law that demands that we conceal our true nature!
讓我們活在恐懼的陰影下的法律
A law that directs those under its dominion to cower in fear
唯恐我們被發現
lest we risk discovery!
我問你  會長女士
I ask you, Madam President.
我問你們所有人
I ask all of you...
這法律保護的是誰
Who does this law protect?
我們
Us?
還是他們
Or them?
我拒絕繼續遵守這項法律
I refuse to bow down any longer.
傲羅們
Aurors,
收回格雷夫斯先生的魔杖
I'd like you to relieve Mr. Graves of his wand
并把他押解回來
and escort him back to...
速速飛來
Accio.
原形顯現
Revelio.
你覺得你能困住我嗎
Do you think you can hold me?
我們會盡全力的
We'll do our best,
格林德沃先生
Mr. Grindelwald.
后會有期
Will we die, just a little?
我看這東西還需要某人照看
I figured somebody oughta keep an eye on this thing.
謝謝你
Thank you.
我們深表歉意  斯卡曼德先生
We owe you an apology, Mr. Scamander.
但是魔法社區被曝光了
But the magical community is exposed!
我們不能抹掉整個城市的記憶
We cannot obliviate an entire city.
其實  我覺得可以
Actually, I think we can.
我還打算帶你一起去亞利桑那州呢
I was intending to wait until we got to Arizona,
但現在看來
but it seems like now
你是我們唯一的希望了  弗蘭克
you are our only hope, Frank.
我也會想你的
I'll miss you too.
你知道該怎么辦
You know what you've got to do.
他們會忘記所有的事情
They won't remember anything.
那個毒液有很強的失憶功能
That venom has incredibly powerful obliviative properties.
我們欠你一個大人情  斯卡曼德先生
We owe you a great debt, Mr. Scamander.
現在  趕緊把你的箱子弄出紐約
Now, get that case out of New York.
遵命  會長女士
Yes, Madam President.
那個麻雞還在這嗎
Is that No-Maj still here?
一忘皆空  不能有特例
Obliviate him. There can be no exceptions.
對不起  就算只有一個人知道
I'm sorry, but even one witness.
你知道法律的
You know the law.
你們自己告別吧
I'll let you say good-bye.
這是最好的結局
This is for the best.
沒錯  我本來
Yeah, I was,
本來就不該在這
I was never even supposed to be here.
我本不該知道任何事情
I was never supposed to know any of this.
大家都知道紐特把我留在他身邊
Everybody knows Newt only kept me around
只是因為
because...
紐特  話說你為什么把我留在身邊
Newt, why did you keep me around?
因為我喜歡你
Because I like you.
你是我的朋友
Because you're my friend
我永遠都不會忘記
and I'll never forget
你是如何幫助我的  雅各布
how you helped me, Jacob.
我會跟著你的
I'll come with you.
我們去別的地方  我們浪跡天涯
We'll go somewhere, we'll go anywhere.
我再也找不到像你一樣的人了
See, I ain't never gonna find anyone like you.
很多人都像我一樣
There's loads like me.
不  不
No. No.
只有你像你一樣
There's only one like you.
我得走了
I gotta go.
-雅各布  -沒事  沒事的
- Jacob! - It's okay. It's okay.
沒事
It's okay.
就像從夢中醒來一樣  對吧
It's just like waking up, right?
很抱歉  對不起
So sorry, sorry!
親愛的科瓦斯基先生
Dear Mr. Kowalski,
您在罐頭廠實在是大材小用
you are wasted in a canning factory.
請把這些鳥蛇的蛋殼
Please take these Occamy eggshells
作為點心屋的擔保
as collateral for your bakery.
一位好心人
A well-wisher.
-這幾天  -我也覺得
- It's been... - Hasn't it?
聽著  紐特  我要感謝你
Listen, Newt, I wanted to thank you.
為什么感謝我
What on earth for?
你知道的  要不是你
Well, you know, if you hadn't said
替我跟皮奎里女士說好話
all those nice things to Madam Picquery about me,
我現在也不可能重新成為傲羅
I wouldn't be back on the investigative team now.
非要被調查的話
Well, I can't think of
被任何人都不如被你調查好
anyone that I'd rather have investigating me.
-最好還是盡量別被調查吧  -我會的
- Try not to need investigating for a bit. - I will.
從今以后我想過安定的生活
Quiet life for me from now on.
回去之后
Back to the Ministry.
-我會發表我的作品  -我很期待
- Deliver my manuscript. - I'll look out for it.
《神奇動物在哪里》
Fantastic Beasts and Where to Find Them.
麗塔·萊斯特蘭奇喜歡讀書嗎
Does Leta Lestrange like to read?
-誰  -你隨身攜帶的照片里的姑娘
- Who? - The girl whose picture you carry.
人是會變的
I don't really know
現在麗塔喜歡什么我也不知道
what Leta likes these days, because people change.
-沒錯  -我反正是變了
- Yes. - I've changed.
我想  或許一點點吧
I think. Maybe a little.
可以的話  能允許我送你一本新書嗎
I'll send you a copy of my book, if I may.
那太好了
I'd like that.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
如果是我親自送來給你呢
How would you feel if I gave you your copy in person?
那樣更好
I'd like that.
我非常期待
Very much.
你的創意來自哪里啊
Where do you get your ideas from,
-科瓦斯基先生  -我也不知道
- Mr. Kowalski? - I don't know.
我也不明白  突發奇想吧
I don't know. They just come.
給  別忘了這個  好好享用吧
Here you go. Don't forget this. Enjoy.
喂  亨利  儲藏室鑰匙
Hey, Henry, storage, all right?
謝啦  伙計
Thanks, pal.